(Leonard:)I got to call her before
I forget how I said it.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
(Penny:)-Hi. What's up?
-How's it going?
(Leonard:)You taking Hollywood by storm?
(Penny:)Actually,
I'm at The Cheesecake Factory.
(Leonard:)You got your job back.
That is great news.
(Leonard:)I didn't want to say anything,
but you are making the right choice.
(Leonard:)To plunge yourself into debt right
now would be literally insane.
(Penny:)Yeah. I'm just
returning my uniform.
(Leonard:)And I support you.
(Voice:)Before we begin your
guided meditation,
(Voice:)close your eyes and picture
yourself in a peaceful environment.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)I'm inside the CERN super collider.
(Voice:)Now, take a deep, relaxing
breath in through your nose.
(Voice:)And let it out.
(Sheldon:)Wow. Didn't see that coming.